# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)



Question.create(question: "How many seasons of Friends are there?", answer1: "Ten Seasons", answer2: "Eight Seasons.", answer3: "Nine Seasons.", answer4: "Eleven Seasons.", correct_answer: "Ten seasons.")
Question.create(question: "Joey played Dr. Drake Ramoray on which soap opera show?", answer1: "E.R.", answer2: "Baywatch.", answer3: "Days of Our Lives.", answer4: "The Golden Girls", correct_answer: "Days of Our Lives.")
Question.create(question: "How many times did Ross get divorced?", answer1: "Two.", answer2: "Three.", answer3: "Four.", answer4: "Five.", correct_answer: "Three.")
Question.create(question: "What store does Phoebe hate?", answer1: "Hobby Lobby.", answer2: "Bed, Bath and Beyond.", answer3: "Pottery Barn.", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Pottery Barn.")
Question.create(question: "Rachel got a job with which company in Paris?", answer1: "Dior.", answer2: "Louis Vuitton.", answer3: "Macy's.", answer4: "Bloomingdale's.", correct_answer: "Louis Vuitton.")
Question.create(question: "What are the names of Ross and Monica’s parents?", answer1: "David and Sarah Geller", answer2: "John and Judy Geller", answer3: "Jack and Jill Geller", answer4: "Jack and Judy Geller.", correct_answer: "Jack and Judy Geller.")
Question.create(question: "What was the occupation of Rachel’s fiancé Barry Farber?", answer1: "Orthodontist.", answer2: "Dentist.", answer3: "Anesthesiologist.", answer4: "Radiologist", correct_answer: "Orthodontist.")
Question.create(question: "Who was the maid of honor at Monica’s wedding?", answer1: "Pheobe.", answer2: "Rachel.", correct_answer: "Rachel.")
Question.create(question: "Phoebe’s scientist boyfriend David worked in what city?", answer1: "Slutsk.", answer2: "Gomel.", answer3: "Minsk.", answer4: "Belarus.", correct_answer: "Minsk.")
Question.create(question: "Monica dated an ophthalmologist named?", answer1: "Richard.", answer2: "Michael.", answer3: "Jason.", answer4: "Paul.", correct_answer: "Richard.")
Question.create(question: "Which Sprouse brother played Ross’ son Ben?", answer1: "Dylan.", answer2: "Cole.", correct_answer: "Cole.")
Question.create(question: "True or false, Rachel kissed all of her Friends (male and female) on the show?", answer1: "True.", answer2: "False.", correct_answer: "True.")
Question.create(question: "What is Chandler Bing’s middle name?", answer1: "Agnes.", answer2: "Edith.", answer3: "Elspeth.", answer4: "Muriel.", correct_answer: "Muriel.")
Question.create(question: "Who pees on Monica after she is stung by a jellyfish?", answer1: "Joey.", answer2: "Chandler.", correct_answer: "Chandler.")
Question.create(question: "What is the name of Phoebe’s twin sister?", answer1: "Ursula.", answer2: "Ariel.", answer3: "Flounder.", answer4: "Sebastien.", correct_answer: "Ursula.")
Question.create(question: "Ross says whose name at the altar in London?", answer1: "Carol.", answer2: "Rachel.", answer3: "Emily.", answer4: "Susan.", correct_answer: "Rachel.")
Question.create(question: "Which member of the British royal family appeared on Friends?", answer1: "William Windsor/Duke of Cambridge", answer2: "Andrew Windsor/Duke of York", answer3: "Sarah Ferguson/Duchess of York.", answer4: "Kate Middleton/Duchess of Cambridge", correct_answer: "Sarah Ferguson/Duchess of York.")
Question.create(question: "Brad Pitt and David Schwimmer’s characters cofounded what club in high school?", answer1: "The 'Rachel Green Sucks Club.'", answer2: "The 'I Hate Rachel Green Club.'", correct_answer: "The 'I Hate Rachel Green Club.'")
Question.create(question: "Which of Joey’s sisters did Chandler fool around with?", answer1: "Mary Angela.", answer2: "Tina.", answer3: "Dina.", answer4: "Mary Teresa.", correct_answer: "Mary Angela.")
Question.create(question: "Who was Joey’s imaginary childhood friend? ", answer1: "Toby.", answer2: "Michael.", answer3: "Maurice.", answer4: "John.", correct_answer: "Maurice.")
Question.create(question: "What was the profession of Joey’s imaginary friend?", answer1: "Space Pilot.", answer2: "Space Racer.", answer3: "Space Pirate.", answer4: "Space Cowboy.", correct_answer: "Space Cowboy.")
Question.create(question: "What was Monica’s nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?", answer1: "Rachel Green's fat friend.", answer2: "Big Fat Goalie.", answer3: "Mon.", answer4: "Harmonica.", correct_answer: "Big Fat Goalie.")
Question.create(question: "What does Rachel guess Chandler’s job is?", answer1: "A transporter.", answer2: "A transponster.", answer3: "A data analyst.", answer4: "A salesman.", correct_answer: "A transponster.")
Question.create(question: "What is Richard’s daughter’s name?", answer1: "Michelle.", answer2: "Sarah.", answer3: "Susan.", answer4: "Carol", correct_answer: "Michelle.")
Question.create(question: "Who is Joey’s agent?", answer1: "Agnes.", answer2: "Stella.", answer3: "Sharon.", answer4: "Estelle.", correct_answer: "Estelle.")
Question.create(question: "Who mistakingly threw a woman’s wooden leg into a fire?", answer1: "Chandler.", answer2: "Ross.", answer3: "Pheobe.", answer4: "Joey.", correct_answer: "Joey.")
Question.create(question: "What was the name of Chandler and Ross’ college band?", answer1: "No Way Dudes.", answer2: "Way, No Way.", answer3: "Far out.", answer4: "The Flock.", correct_answer: "Way, No Way.")
Question.create(question: "Monica categorizes her towels into how many categories?", answer1: "11.", answer2: "8.", answer3: "14.", answer4: "7", correct_answer: "11.")
Question.create(question: "Ross and Rachel’s wedding dinner was held where in Vegas?", answer1: "A Denny's.", answer2: "A Pizza Hut.", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "A Pizza Hut.")
Question.create(question: "Joey and Chandler’s TV guide is addressed to who?", answer1: "Mr. Chandler Bong.", answer2: "Sir. Chanandler Bong.", answer3: "Miss Chanandler Bong.", answer4: "Chandler Bong.", correct_answer: "Miss Chanandler Bong.")
Question.create(question: "What was the name of Ross’ pet monkey?", answer1: "Marvin.", answer2: "Marley.", answer3: "Marcel.", answer4: "Marso.", correct_answer: "Marcel.")
Question.create(question: "According to Monica, a woman has how many erogenous zones?", answer1: "Five.", answer2: "Six.", answer3: "Seven.", answer4: "Eight.", correct_answer: "Seven.")

Question.create(question: "What does Phoebe legally change her name to after her wedding?", answer1: "Princess Consulea Banana Hammock.", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Princess Consulea Banana Hammock.")
Question.create(question: "What does Mike change his name to in response to Phoebe's name change?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Crap Bag.")
Question.create(question: "What form of self-defense does Ross try to teach Rachel and Phoebe?", answer1: "Sashimi.", answer2: "Unagi.", answer3: "Negiri.", answer4: "Umami.", correct_answer: "Unagi.")
Question.create(question: "What song makes Ross and Rachel’s daughter Emma laugh for the first time?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Sir Mix-a-Lot’s “Baby Got Back.”")
Question.create(question: "What is the name of Joey’s stuffed penguin?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Hugsy.")
Question.create(question: "What caused the fire at Rachel and Phoebe’s apartment?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Rachel’s hair straightener.")
Question.create(question: "Phoebe is a surrogate for who?", answer1: "Chandler and Monica.", answer2: "Frank Jr. and his wife Alice.", answer3: "Ursula and her husband Jason.", answer4: "Her homeless friends Don and Christy.", correct_answer: "Frank Jr. and his wife Alice.")
Question.create(question: "What color is Monica’s apartment?", answer1: "Pink.", answer2: "Beige.", answer3: "Grey.", answer4: "Purple.", correct_answer: "Purple.")
Question.create(question: "How many sisters does Joey have?", answer1: "Six.", answer2: "Seven.", answer3: "Eight.", answer4: "Nine.", correct_answer: "Seven.")
Question.create(question: "Joey doesn’t share what?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Food.")
Question.create(question: "What do Monica and Chandler name their twins?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Erica and Jack.")
Question.create(question: "Ross’ first wife Carol leaves him for who?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Susan Bunch.")
Question.create(question: "What is the name of Chandler’s father’s Las Vegas all-male burlesque?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Viva Las Gaygas.")
Question.create(question: "Phoebe attempts to teach Joey what language?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "French.")
Question.create(question: "Chick Jr. and Duck Jr. got stuck in what?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "A foosball table.")
Question.create(question: "Who was married to a supposedly gay Canadian ice dancer named Duncan?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Phoebe.")
Question.create(question: "Rachel was in which sorority?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Kappa Kappa Delta.")
Question.create(question: "What are the names of Rachel’s sisters?", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "Jill and Amy.")
Question.create(question: "Which character famously said, 'PIVOT?'", answer1: "Ross.", answer2: "Chandler.", answer3: "Rachel.", answer4: "Joey.", correct_answer: "Ross.")
Question.create(question: "Phoebe finds what in her soda can?", answer1: "An ear.", answer2: "A thumb.", answer3: "A nose.", answer4: "An eyebrow.", correct_answer: "A thumb.")

Question.create(question: "Who was (accidentally) Monica’s first kiss?", answer1: "Carl.", answer2: "Jack.", answer3: "Chandler.", answer4: "Ross.", correct_answer: "Ross.")
Question.create(question: "Rachel goes on Ross’ honeymoon by herself where?", answer1: "Athens, Greese.", answer2: "Rome, Italy.", answer3: "Paris, France.", answer4: "London, England.", correct_answer: "Athens, Greece.")
Question.create(question: "What holiday does Chandler hate?", answer1: "Easter.", answer2: "Thangsgiving.", answer3: "Christmas.", answer4: "Arbor Day.", correct_answer: "Thanksgiving.")
Question.create(question: "Who was Rachel’s prom date?", answer1: "Chip Matthews.", answer2: "Aaron Matthews.", answer3: "Chip Finnegan.", answer4: "Aaron Finnegan.", correct_answer: "Chip Matthews.")
Question.create(question: "What was the name of Ross and Monica’s dog when they were kids?", answer1: "Chu-Chu.", answer2: "Cho-Cho.", answer3: "Cha-Cha.", answer4: "Chi-Chi.", correct_answer: "Chi-Chi.")
Question.create(question: "What actor played Phoebe’s husband Mike Hannigan?", answer1: "Paul Rudd.", answer2: "Brad Pitt.", correct_answer: "Paul Rudd.")
Question.create(question: "Where did Ross and Rachel have their first date?", answer1: "The museum.", answer2: "The planetarium.", answer3: "The aquarium.", answer4: "The menagerie.", correct_answer: "The planetarium.")
Question.create(question: "How many roses did Ross send Emily?", answer1: "64.", answer2: "96.", answer3: "80.", answer4: "72.", correct_answer: "72.")
Question.create(question: "How many pages was Rachel’s letter to Ross?", answer1: "Sixteen pages (front and back).", answer2: "Seventeen pages (front and back).", answer3: "Eighteen pages (front and back).", answer4: "Nineteen pages (front and back).", correct_answer: "Eighteen pages (front and back).")
Question.create(question: "What year did Friends first premiere?", answer1: "1993.", answer2: "1994.", answer3: "1995.", answer4: "1996.", correct_answer: "1994.")
Question.create(question: "Joey’s Cabbage Patch Kid is named what?", answer1: "Alicia May Emory.", answer2: "Carly Rae Jepsen.", answer3: "Haley Joel Osment.", answer4: "Aaron Taylor Johnson.", correct_answer: "Alicia May Emory.")
Question.create(question: "What was the name of the game Chandler made up to give Joey money?", answer1: "Spoons.", answer2: "Forks.", answer3: "Cups.", answer4: "Plates.", correct_answer: "Cups.")
Question.create(question: "In an effort to get over Richard, Monica started making what?", answer1: "Candy.", answer2: "Chocolate.", answer3: "Cookies.", answer4: "Jam.", correct_answer: "Jam.")
Question.create(question: "What fruit is Ross allergic to?", answer1: "Strawberries.", answer2: "Kiwi.", answer3: "Watermelon.", answer4: "Peaches.", correct_answer: "Kiwi.")
Question.create(question: "What is Rachel’s favorite flower?", answer1: "Roses.", answer2: "Lilacs.", answer3: "Lillies.", answer4: "Violets.", correct_answer: "Lillies.")
Question.create(question: "What was the name of Ross and Rachel’s male nanny?", answer1: "Dakota.", answer2: "Kelly.", answer3: "Sandy.", answer4: "Bailey.", correct_answer: "Sandy.")
Question.create(question: "Who came on to who in The One With The Videotape?", answer1: "Rachel came on to Ross.", answer2: "Ross came on to Rachel.", correct_answer: "Rachel came on to Ross.")
Question.create(question: "What was Joey’s nickname when he was working at Alessandro’s?", answer1: "Centaur.", answer2: "Dragon.", answer3: "Sphinx.", answer4: "Phoenix.", correct_answer: "Dragon.")
Question.create(question: "Monica worked as a waitress at what diner?", answer1: "Moondance Diner.", answer2: "Sundance Diner.", answer3: "Riverdance Diner.", answer4: "Disco Dance Diner.", correct_answer: "Moondance Diner.")
Question.create(question: "What was Rachel’s bra size?", answer1: "30B.", answer2: "32B.", answer3: "30C.", answer4: "32C.", correct_answer: "32C.")



=begin

Question.create(question: "", answer1: "", answer2: "", answer3: "", answer4: "", correct_answer: "")





71. Question: Ross worked as a professor at what school?
Answer: New York University.

72. Question: What word did Rachel misspell on her resume?
Answer: Computer.

73. Question: What are the names of the triplets Phoebe gives birth to?
Answer: Frank Jr. Jr., Leslie and Chandler.

74. Question: Who said, “See, he’s her lobster!”
Answer: Phoebe.

75. Question: What city is Friends set in?
Answer: New York City.

76. Question: What is the first wedding gift Monica opens?
Answer: A tiny salt shaker.

77. Question: Rachel’s sister Amy decides she wants to become what after babysitting Emma?
Answer: A baby stylist.

78. Question: Ross and Carol were busted having sex on which Disney ride?
Answer: It’s a Small World.

79. Question: Which Friend entered a Vanilla Ice lookalike contest and won?
Answer: Chandler.

80. Question: True or false, Monica ate macaroni off a jewelry box she made.
Answer: True.

81. Question: What ingredient did Rachel mistakingly put in her Thanksgiving trifle?
Answer: Beef.

82. Question: Phoebe thought “Kenny the Copy Guy” was who?
Answer: Ralph Lauren.


83. Question: What is the name of Joey’s barcalounger?
Answer: Rosita.

84. Question: Who dated a college student named Elizabeth Stevens?
Answer: Ross.

85. Question: Monica could not tell time until what age?
Answer: 13.

Parade Daily
Celebrity interviews, recipes and health tips delivered to your inbox.

Email Address
 
86. Question: Phoebe created a three-dimensional picture of a woman named?
Answer: Gladys.

87. Question: Who was the last Friend to find out about Monica and Chandler’s relationship?
Answer: Ross.

88. Question: Chandler and Joey both dated an actress named?
Answer: Kathy.

89. Question: What did Monica want from Phoebe as an engagement present?
Answer: Her grandmother’s cookie recipe.

90. Question: Who had a pony and a boat at age 15?
Answer: Rachel.

91. Question: Phoebe said something was wrong with the right or the left phalange of Rachel’s plane?
Answer: The left.

92. Question: Who is Santa’s friend that Ross invents to teach Ben about Hanukkah?
Answer: The Holiday Armadillo.

93. Question: Who is the youngest Friend?
Answer: Rachel.

94. Question: Chandler told Janice he was moving where to avoid seeing her again?
Answer: Yemen.

95. Question: Who introduced Phoebe and Mike?
Answer: Joey.

96. Question: Phoebe’s grandmother said she got her cookie recipe from her grandmother named?
Answer: Nestle Toulouse (AKA Nestlé Toll House).

97. Question: The Geller Cup was a trophy for which sport?
Answer: Touch football games.

98. Question: Joey’s stalker Erika Ford was played by which actress?
Answer: Brooke Shields.

99. Question: Who did Monica forget to invite to Rachel’s baby shower?
Answer: Rachel’s mother Sandra.

100. Question: Which of Monica’s boyfriends wanted to become the Ultimate Fighting Champion?
Answer: Pete (Peter Becker).

101. Question: What was the name of the lipstick brand for men that Joey starred in a Japanese commercial for?
Answer: Ichiban.

102. Question: Ross, Susan and Phoebe got stuck where before Ben’s birth?
Answer: A closet.

103. Question: Who gave Phoebe away at her wedding?
Answer: Chandler.

104. Question: Monica and Chandler first got together where?
Answer: London.

105. Question: The handcuffs that were found in Rachel’s former room belonged to who?
Answer: Monica and Ross’ Nana (grandmother).

106. Question: Chandler and Ross helped Joey practice for what game show audition?
Answer: Bamboozled.

107. Question: What does Chandler call the Paris of Oklahoma?
Answer: Tulsa.

108. Question: What food caused Ross to get sick on Space Mountain?
Answer: Tacos.

109. Question: Who is older Ross or Monica?
Answer: Ross.

110. Question: What is actually Rachel’s favorite movie?
Answer: Weekend at Bernie’s.

111. Question: Which Friend had a traumatic swing incident at age 4?
Answer: Rachel.

112. Question: Ross and Rachel’s daughter Emma would have turned 18 what year?
Answer: 2020.

113. Question: Which Friend didn’t go to London for Ross’ wedding?
Answer: Phoebe.

114. Question: What kind of bed did the Mattress King deliver to Monica?
Answer: A racecar bed.

115. Question: Emma’s first birthday cake was supposed to be shaped like what?
Answer: A bunny.

116. Question: In what part of her body did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?
Answer: Her ear.

117. Question: Ross created a comic book called what?
Answer: Science Boy.

118. Question: What is Chandler’s surname?
Answer: Bing.

119. Question: What is Joey’s favorite food?
Answer: Sandwiches.

120. Question: How old was Chandler when he first touched a girl’s breast?
Answer: 19.

121. Question: What is Monica’s biggest pet peeve?
Answer: Animals dressed as humans.

122. Question: Which Friend had his/her identity stolen?
Answer: Monica.

123. Question: Joey doesn’t read which book without making sure there is plenty of room in the freezer?
Answer: The Shining.

124. Question: What is the name of Ross and Monica’s maternal grandmother?
Answer: Althea.

125. Question: Who stole all the insoles out of Chandler’s shoes?
Answer: Chandler’s roomate Eddie.

126. Question: Who gave Rachel and Ross the name “Emma” for their daughter?
Answer: Monica.

127. Question: Joey was cast as the butt double for which actor?
Answer: Al Pacino.

Related: A Friends Reunion Is Coming! HBO Max Confirms the Unscripted Special

128.  Question: What is the name of Phoebe’s alter ego?
Answer: Regina Phalange.


129. Question: What year did the series finale of Friends air?
Answer: 2004.

130. Question: What is the name of Rachel and Monica’s building superintendent?
Answer: Mr. Treeger.

131. Question: What is Joey’s pin number?
Answer: 5639.

132. Question: What was the last state that Ross couldn’t remember?
Answer: Delaware.

133. Question: What was the name of Chandler’s roommate prior to Joey?
Answer: Kip.

134. Question: Whose idea was it to get married in Vegas, Rachel or Ross’?
Answer: Rachel.

135. Question: What was the name of Monica’s imaginary boyfriend?
Answer: Jared.

136. Question: What kind of plastic surgery did Rachel have?
Answer: A nose job.

137. Question: Who was called Sir Limps-a-Lot after losing a toe?
Answer: Chandler.

138. Question: What was the name of Rachel’s hairless cat?
Answer: Mrs. Whiskerson.

139. Question: Which balloon got away during the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade in Season 1?
Answer: Underdog.

140. Question: Who gave birth to Chandler and Monica’s twins?
Answer: Erica.

141. Question: Chandler and Rachel ate cheesecake off the floor from what bakery?  
Answer: Mama’s Little Bakery.

142. Question: Which Friend once mugged Ross?
Answer: Phoebe.

143. Question: Monica, Ross and Rachel attended what high school?
Answer: Lincoln High School.

144. Question: Who were on “a break”?
Answer: Rachel and Ross.

145. Question: What was the name of Monica’s senior prom date?
Answer: Roy Gublik.

146. Question: Ross was jealous of who at Rachel’s job?
Answer: Mark.

147. Question: What was the name of the “hot girl from the Xerox place?”
Answer: Chloe.

148. Question: What did Rachel get a tattoo of?
Answer: A heart.

149. Question: Who is the first Friend to speak on the show?
Answer: Monica.

150. Question: Who sings the Friends theme song “I’ll Be There for You?”
Answer: The Rembrandts.
=end